Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
[Between Love and Frost]
[Episode 9]
How come you're here?
Why did you do this?
Pei, I love you.
I've always loved you.
I can do anything for you.
I'll never leave you.
I should be the one for you.
Pei,
how could you be so heartless to me?
вҷӘLove is an abyss one cannot escapeвҷӘ
вҷӘThe more I doubt, the more I fearвҷӘ
вҷӘSparks of hatred
ignite within the heartвҷӘ
вҷӘThe more I struggle,
the hoarser my voice becomesвҷӘ
вҷӘI guard myself over and over againвҷӘ
вҷӘI hesitate in every word
and every momentвҷӘ
вҷӘI feign, struggleвҷӘ
вҷӘFlee, and breakвҷӘ
вҷӘThe endless shackle of darknessвҷӘ
Keep the change.
Thank you, sir.
вҷӘLet the hatred goвҷӘ
вҷӘDon't dwellвҷӘ
I can protect you!
Only me!
вҷӘLet love and hate
scatter with the windвҷӘ
вҷӘLet myself be freeвҷӘ
Only by keeping him as far away
as possible,
can I seek revenge.
Your hand
is injured.
As a grown-up,
you can't even take care of yourself.
I'll never feel at ease
leaving you to others.
Tongce
isn't as handsome as me,
nor nearly as witty and charming.
If it came down to a fight,
he'd never stand a chance against me.
Pei,
since you love the wretch so much,
just die together with her!
Chu Minghui,
I know
you have to seek revenge.
But after avenging,
you'll have your long life ahead.
All I wish
is that whoever stands beside you then,
you'll live a free
and happy life.
Thank you for your blessings.
I'm going back now.
вҷӘLove is an abyss one cannot escapeвҷӘ
вҷӘThe more I doubt, the more I fearвҷӘ
Gu Tongpei!
вҷӘThe more I struggle,
the hoarser my voice becomesвҷӘ
вҷӘI guard myself over and over againвҷӘ
вҷӘI hesitate in every word
and every momentвҷӘ
вҷӘI feign, struggleвҷӘ
вҷӘFlee, and breakвҷӘ
вҷӘThe endless shackle of darknessвҷӘ
вҷӘLet the hatred goвҷӘ
вҷӘDon't dwellвҷӘ
вҷӘOnly when flowers wither
will scars formвҷӘ
вҷӘLet love and hate
scatter with the windвҷӘ
вҷӘLet myself be freeвҷӘ
What does this kiss mean?
You do care about me, don't you?
I understand.
I understand everything.
I won't pressure you.
Don't be afraid.
You're hurt.
Let's hurry back and tend to it.
Come on.
Let's go home.
As long as you're here,
even if I suffer grave injuries,
I'll surely heal quickly.
Don't say such foolish things!
From now on,
take good care of yourself.
Never let yourself be hurt easily again.
I promise to protect myself,
and I will give my all
to keep you safe.
The bomber's been found.
It's Chu Yan.
Keep her under tight watch.
With leverage this significant,
we must seize the opportunity.
Yes.
Mr. Gu,
based on Miss Chu's intel,
we've contacted Mr. Chu.
He's agreed to ransom her
with a crate of gold.
The exchange is set for tonight
at seven at the nightclub.
Great.
Prepare to move.
I'll make this trip myself tonight.
Yes.
I'll help you capture Chu Huaixuan.
Don't trouble yourself with my matters.
What I mean is
we shall not let Gu Tongce learn
we're working together.
I'm afraid he'll target you again.
I know you're protecting me.
But promise me this,
never put yourself
in danger for my sake.
I understand that nothing changes
until you capture Chu Huaixuan.
So pursue him with everything
you've got.
I won't hinder you.
When all is settled,
we'll have a lot of time.
[Palace of Joy]
Who's there?
Sorry to interrupt.
I must've been overthinking.
My apologies.
I just had no choice
but to act that way,
asking you to kiss me.
It's alright.
I'll follow your lead.
Why are you here?
And you?
Playing dumb.
I was worried about you.
I tailed you from afar
to keep an eye out.
Lucky I did!
You were in peril back there.
But I told you...
I know.
I promised
I won't hinder you.
Don't worry. Without your order,
I won't act recklessly.
Thank you.
But your father murdered my mother.
I can't abandon my revenge,
not even for you.
вҷӘLove is an abyss one cannot escapeвҷӘ
вҷӘThe more I doubt, the more I fearвҷӘ
вҷӘSparks of hatred
ignite within the heartвҷӘ
вҷӘThe more I struggle,
the hoarser my voice becomesвҷӘ
вҷӘI guard myself over and over againвҷӘ
вҷӘI hesitate in every word
and every momentвҷӘ
вҷӘI feign, struggleвҷӘ
вҷӘFlee, and breakвҷӘ
вҷӘThe endless shackle of darknessвҷӘ
вҷӘLet the hatred goвҷӘ
вҷӘDon't dwellвҷӘ
вҷӘOnly when flowers wither
will scars formвҷӘ
вҷӘLet love and hate
scatter with the windвҷӘ
вҷӘLet myself be freeвҷӘ